---
title: 'Preguntas Frecuentes'
frequentQuestion:
    -
        question: 'How can I buy a jewel from Vega Navascués?'
        answer: dasdasdasdasd
    -
        question: 'What characteristics does silver have?'
        answer: daasdadasdas
    -
        question: 'What does the term "sterling silver" mean?'
        answer: adsadasdas
    -
        question: '¿Qué tipos de plata hay?'
        answer: asdasdad
    -
        question: 'What types of silver are there?'
        answer: dasdas
    -
        question: 'Why is silver oxidized?'
        answer: adasda
    -
        question: 'What factors can cause silver to rust?'
        answer: sadadas
    -
        question: 'How can I care for a silver piece with patina?'
        answer: dasdada
    -
        question: 'Are there differences between ring sizes for men and women?'
        answer: asdasdasd
    -
        question: 'Is it possible to change the size of a ring?'
        answer: asdasdasd
    -
        question: 'Do all jewelers use the same ring size scale?'
        answer: asdsadasd
    -
        question: 'How can I find out my ring size?'
        answer: dadasda
---

